they said your mummy and daddy said it's
almost time for school we need to get
ready to go I'm not going to school
today Gerald just who are the boys what
are they after this is what I must know
why do they Harbor such a deep hatred
for Sonic Underground you're going
somewhere but I thought we were going to
have but sex I can't today Gerald you go
to school without me tell the teacher in
busy or that in taking a huge ass dump
on the toilet
Sid is this about the prophecy that you
dreamt about a week ago I can't tell you
anymore gerald I already told you too
much if word got out that told you this
you would become a target for the enemy
don't worry about me it'll be back
before you know it you sexy boy
I'll [ __ ] your ass when I get back
what the [ __ ] let go of me you weird
pink [ __ ] I ain't letting you go until
you [ __ ] me in the ass right here you
said you would [ __ ] me in the ass today
so keep your promise you sexy yellow boy
I didn't promise you [ __ ] [ __ ] Pluto
before I beat your [ __ ] ass we are
like three years old [ __ ] what the [ __ ]
is wrong with you mommy daddy
Gerald's trying to rape me
[Music]
damn you you you son of a [ __ ] you
killed my boyfriend I'll kill all you
[ __ ] do you hear me boys I'll kill
every last one of you I won't stop until
you are all dead
[Music]
pushes my clothes are on fire
[Applause]
[Music]
at least my tricycle wasn't destroyed in
the explosion
[Music]
how are you kids enjoying the chili dogs
I paid extra for the spicy chili this
week they're okay but I like the dollar
store chili even better mom where's my
tofu dog is it done yet I'm starving
like a [ __ ] yaar it's almost finished
Sonia get your plate ready all right it
seems to be done come get it while it's
hot
give me that [ __ ] gimme gimme gimme
[Music]
what's going on internet a toaster chili
dogs for breakfast
damn Nicki no soma teens [ __ ] God hey
hey Elena let me borrow the car
fine but don't be gone late because I
need it for work this afternoon what a
bit of it a market are these for my
chili those following a hit smack
Charles why does your bit [ __ ] stink
did you not wipe your huge smelly ass
when you got out of the bathroom earlier
not believe in me uh-uh of course a we
paid me would walk all four hit or we
pay after that you know has me he'll
tell me the truth now or I will have
Manny come over here and sniff your ass
to find out oh no I ain't that has
[ __ ] stinks okay Finley your voice I
raped booty didn't aviato blog don't you
say a telecourse story is closing in 45
mi notice if he were at that if he
didn't weep Amyas equals survey team and
get ready for it close
whoopsie I am very sorry about your door
sometimes the force is too powerful even
for me to handle obi-wan and Sportacus
what are you two doing here we have come
to finally tell you about the prophecy
the truth and all of the secrets that
have been hid from you until now
everyone please take a seat this is
quite a long story but you must pay
attention I insist on a boutique a
newbie hospital team Terry no Graham
back yes it's their destiny to know this
they should know they have to know this
long ago the planet Mobius lived in
peace but for a fat man showed up I'm
sure you all know him
his name is dr. Robotnik the evil tyrant
who overthrew your family and became the
import in just one night
even though you fought valiantly the
battle was lost the Royal forces were no
match for the fat man's army of
swat-bots
with nothing more that could be done the
rulers left their homeland praying to
God that they wouldn't be hunted down
and killed like [ __ ]
the Queen's Trevis Sonic Manic and Sonya
were separated and to be hidden away so
that in the future they can come
together and defeat Robotnik bringing
back peace to the world as the years
went on the Hedgehogs grew up and
learned the truth they knew they
couldn't just sit by and let Robotnik
rule over the land with an iron fist the
Hedgehogs grew and so did their skills
in combat eventually the time came they
were ready to challenge the evil
Robotnik and one final showdown they
fought with their lives ready to put an
end to the suffering that dr. Robotnik
put on so many people but most
importantly their family after a
hard-fought battle the Hedgehogs were
victorious
Robotnik's reign was over the Royal
Hedgehog Family reclaimed their throne
and returned as Mobius rightful rulers
however the cause of what Robotnik did
Mobius was beyond repair everything
wasn't ruined there was only one thing
the people of Mobius could do they left
Mobius in search of new land became
across earth and made it their new home
but then a threat even greater than the
fat man will rise for young huge white
boys who want revenge against the Sonic
Underground but you need not fear for
when all hope is lost a blade of pure
white light can be seen from the horizon
and a man with beautiful blond hair will
show up and take the name of Sportacus
and that my friends is the story of the
prophecy the boys are now waiting for us
to show up to their locations for one
last fight and all out more about to the
[ __ ] death
you're [ __ ] [ __ ] if you think I'm
letting you take my baby girl into
battle take Sonic with you he is fat and
nobody even likes him way of autonomy
notice Elena were created to simmer and
know it hastily ustedes frightened the
fat uncle is right you have to do this
for all of us but you won't be alone I
got help
this is it one of our allies he has done
extensive research on the boys in
Buddhist Costa boy ha I may be 3 years
old but that doesn't stop me from being
a [ __ ] scientist sit did you find the
location of the boys with your leapfrog
laptop you can bet your butt cheeks they
are waiting for us to arrive as we speak
and lucky for you guys I picked up some
friends on the way here Max
Trevor Cyrus what are you guys doing
here don't forget Sonic that we are
Sonic Underground characters too
this war involves us all thanks dude
these boys won't stand a chance against
freedom fighters like us digital
avowedly oh wait it's vut Evan you are
forgetting someone old man Jared you're
here too of course I'm here why wouldn't
I be the boys bait they took my daddy
and now they are telling me that they
won't let him go unless I kill Manic the
Hedgehog you met Zoe she was dating Tito
Joe hey know what confidence having yoga
cuantos every boy this is amazing isn't
it bro
with all these people on our side there
isn't any way we can lose no it still
isn't enough there is still someone we
need on our side if he doesn't join us
we won't stand a chance
ROH I don't understand what do you mean
ro ro lol Oh
alfrid
do you have the data yes the data has
been retrieved I will pass it over to
you now
Alfred you wait out here this won't take
long
yes I will do as you say sir Bartleby
Oh
ha'n't right there you are not to set
foot in here our master has given us
special orders to protect this chamber
with our lives leave this place now or
your buttcheeks will be the next target
for thy blade of justice
put your weapons away your master is ed
no you must be lying our master is alive
it is true your master is ed but his son
is alive and he has come is it true are
you truly the
over 20 years ago our master left
telling us that someday the rightful
heir would arrive and take the sword of
light in his hands
could it be so is the chosen one not him
but his own son instead go on then take
the blade into your hand if it glows
that is proof to us that you are the
rightful owner if not you will die
[Music]
y'know sir when I saw you hold up that
store back there I was reminded of the
old days you look very much like your
father
[Music]
I have no have mother-father
you
thank you so much for the ride mark your
truck is way faster than my bicycle
don't mention it Athair I'll do anything
to help a fellow man you can repay me
for the ride by heading down to the
strip club with me tomorrow morning and
buy me a couple of beers while I [ __ ] a
bunch of [ __ ] in the ass if any [ __ ]
tries to resist me I'll just punch her
in the face and treat her life the woman
sees Mindy I can't believe you're here
already are you here to help us fight
the boys ha ha you bet your ass I am
Sonia could be one kenobi stop by my
house in the middle of the night first
he came into my room and we had sex then
he told me all about the war and the
boys after hearing about all that
there's no way I'm letting my best
friend and her family fight alone
yo Manic where the hell did Sonic run
off to
I saw him hauling ass down the street
don't tell me he's backing out of this
thing even after we're all here to fight
I have no idea nuts maybe he had to take
a massive dump or some [ __ ]
[Music]
Sleet I'm worried for Robotnik he's been
in the bathroom for over three hours is
he going to be okay
how the [ __ ] should I know Dingo this
happens every [ __ ] time we get daca
bail
[Music]
well if it isn't my mortal enemy and my
rival Sonic the Hedgehog of all people
to blow down my wall when I'm taking a
[ __ ] what do you want
don't worry Robotnik I'm not here to
pick a fight with you I'm here to ask
for your help my help what the hell are
you talking about in what world would I
ever help the [ __ ] Robotnik listen to
me
a group of white boys have risen up they
intend to take over the world
you mean like the Jonas Brothers yes but
instead of three of them there's four
and one is dressed as the Green Goblin
from spider-man they called me my sips
my family and even my friends out to
battle with our lives on the line I'm
going to be honest with you Robotnik the
boys they're stronger than you ever were
I don't think even the Sonic Underground
will be able to take them down
like we did to you I know Sonic the
Hedgehog you don't have to tell me
anymore I know about the boys
they came to my house last week telling
me that they intended to kill you and
your friends they threatened me and told
me not to get involved or else they
would kill me too
I wanted to fight back but they had a
gun they they scared me sometimes it's
best to just give up I won't help you
not because you are my enemy
but because I am afraid afraid of the
boys Robotnik surely you must know after
they kill me they will come after you
you and I are both their biggest threats
right now that's why we need to work
together if we don't well do you really
want to become their [ __ ] or are you so
scared that you are willing to accept
your fate even if it means death
get out of my bathroom
I'm disappointed Robotnik of all people
I hope that you would be the one to help
us you use to be powerful you use to be
the ruler of Mobius but now I see that
really was the past I pray that someday
you grow the same pair of balls that you
once had goodbye dr. Robotnik they are
going to kill you you're going to die
[ __ ] I'm sure I will but at least I'm
not going down without a fight
[Music]
Sleet get your fine ass in here boy dr.
Robotnik what was that sound it sounded
like an explosion forget about that
ready the car we're going somewhere
immediately Talyn go to get at least 500
swat-bots ready for battle but your
roundness shouldn't you wipe your ass
first it [ __ ] stinks there is no time
we must go immediately
[Music]
come on bro what's taking so long you
know we don't got all day the whole
world is on the line here
don't make us leave without you fat ass
Manik look there Sonic down the street
bro where the hell were you did you go
behind Kmart and have Bart levy [ __ ] you
in the ass again I went to try and get
reinforcements but unfortunately it
didn't go as planned I'm afraid it's
going to be just us everyone but don't
give up hope as long as we believe in
ourselves and each other nobody will be
able to take us down [ __ ] let's show
those four sexy white boys what happens
when you mess with the Sonic Underground
you
well would you look at that it seems my
[ __ ] is doing a pretty good job at
rallying the troops
Bart levy you're here I've been waiting
for you all day
what took you so long uh-huh sorry for
the wait my Beach but I was a bit busy
as we are going into a battle I felt it
would be wise to grab the legendary
sword of Dresden along the way here the
sword of treason you mean the sword that
was passed down through your family for
countless generations yes the very one
it's the most expensive sword in the
world being made out of pure gold by
real Japanese people and costing five
hundred and six billion dollars thank
God your boyfriend is here Sonic the
cause without him I know you wouldn't be
able to win the world without me after
all the prophecy specifically states
that I will be the one to save the world
the prophecy will not come true unless I
am present is that correct
he'll be one Kenobi yes that is correct
but how do you already know all this
Sidra Science Kid stopped by my mansion
this morning and explained everything
you naughty naughty little boy are you
trying to show off to Bartley be in
front of me perhaps after this war is
over I should take you back to my place
and teach you some manners maybe I'll
even give you a good spanking
watch it like I used to give to my
Padawan and again
oh that's right please forgive me I
forgot that your [ __ ] Gerald had just
died but I was doing certainly wasn't
the jet Iowa was it but you know
latching on to the Past like you're
doing is also against the Jedi Code it
doesn't bother me that you're only three
years old H is just a number after all
Edom on 20 looped obi-wan Whitney was a
I'm livin at Indy you're right Sportacus
we should really haul ass the boys are
waiting for us but before we go we need
to find a convenient form of
transportation my Jedi Starfighter can't
carry all of us
does anybody have a big car or some [ __ ]
I don't know about you [ __ ] but I
know a perfect form of Transportation
does anybody else got Healy's haha
who doesn't
yo Max you got a cassette player in that
funky little fanny pack of yours what do
you say we listen to some sick beats on
the way to the battlefield
[Music]
yamaneika do you think we'll be serving
LaVon become a couple of mostly I'd like
yet that sounds like a good idea Spratt
haggis we're gonna need some monster to
refuel
give us every monster energy drink
you've got
hey do you [ __ ] Nair me to take a big
smelly dump on this [ __ ] car driver
please don't do this you're going to get
us into trouble nobody thinks you're
cool for taking a [ __ ] on a stranger's
car [ __ ] you [ __ ] I'm the coolest
[ __ ] around quick pull out your
phones and record this I can feel the
poop slipping out of my butt Trevor look
out there's a car
obi-wan Lehtonen really yoga day I mean
Charles Hedgehog I sense I sense a great
disturbance in the force
it felt as though a [ __ ] [ __ ]
about to take a [ __ ] dump on
somebody's car was shot down in cold
blood by somebody in a purple car
what the hell happened out here somebody
somebody was driving by and and they and
they shot Trevor
Trevor's dead Sonic it was the boys I
know it
they made Trevor their [ __ ]
[Music]
[Applause]
just how many friends are we going to
lose before this war is over
[Music]
great shot Doka it looks like you killed
the one who was pooping on the car where
are we going next joka what do you think
we're going bigs range the bow feel to
me and for the boys I'm crazy
you
come on my blue bro it's about time we
head to the battlefield if we stay here
there is a chance that the boys will
drive back around and kill all of us
Manik is right Sonic we don't have the
time to warn the Fallen right now
Trevor he that son of a [ __ ] knew what
he was signing up for when he came along
but he the fact that it even starts yet
Trevor didn't deserve to go out this way
no one does xiu'er Trevor went out like
a [ __ ] but let it be a lesson bro that
we need to be stronger than him you guys
head to the battlefield without me how
you got to go back inside and take a
[ __ ]
[Music]
[Applause]
kid what's wrong where are you crying
did you [ __ ] your pants where are your
parents
[Music]
you
Bart levy what the hell was that are you
okay of course I'm okay [ __ ] the boys
just left me a little present in the
bathroom and it wasn't [ __ ] it's a good
thing I was the one who stepped in there
and not any of you it didn't affect me
at all because of my huge muscles if any
of you happen to step in there instead
of me there's no doubt you would have
died well what is everybody standing
around for
we have a battlefield to get to
ah b1 Sportacus are you sure that this
is the place
I'm 99.8% positive Sonic I hacked into a
satellite for the United States
government using Miley front computer if
my calculations are correct which they
always are the boys are here somewhere
Sonic look over there those must be the
boys see really far off in the distance
there's four of them just like hobby wad
said there are
what's up Elena Domingo yo Rico miss any
of them yeah I recognize that [ __ ] in
the blue vest he's a cashier from Walnut
he hates me because he thinks I ran over
his little brothers bike or some [ __ ]
he's been sending me and the kids death
threats in the mail for the past year I
think his name is Charlie
hey guys is it just me or does that one
kid in the middle look like Billy from
school I think you're right Manik that
does look like Billy but what is he
doing here
I mean sure he tried to rape you one
time Manik but he's always been a fan of
the Sonic Underground
he looks pretty sad too do you think the
boys are making him do this it doesn't
matter if they are or not we're still
going to kill every [ __ ] one of them
they're holding back that's easy for you
to say Bart levy my lover but but I'm
not strong like you I'm just a weak
little boy when the time comes I don't
know if I have the heart to kill even if
it's to kill for what I believe in and
[ __ ] don't you tell us you're giving up
already Sonic it's not over yet
you know we we all still have a goal to
achieve and we can achieve that piece of
ass together it's an honor to finally
meet you Sonic the Hedgehog I am Kyoto
Kamini Sonic Underground is everybody's
childhood in this fight you are not
alone we will not stand by as you throw
yourselves into the hell of battle it's
our job as your fans to be your shield
and your [ __ ] so if you would allow it
please let us assist you in this faded
fight that will determine the fate of
the universe very wise
welcome aboard [ __ ] oh [ __ ] everybody
look over there in the sky I think it's
a group of people and it looks like they
are flying on broomsticks
no that isn't just anyone it's Harry
Potter and look Professor Dumbledore is
there too
see Ron Weasley and Hermione I told you
some deep [ __ ] was going on so the
battle hasn't started yet that's good I
guess we made it in time see Albus
Dumbledore Oh DDO you know we're all
very why that's simple my friend
Professor Snape is a huge Sonic
Underground fan much like us all he told
me that we felt unusual like he had to
take a poop that no it was fine from
that I could feel that something
important was happening here would you
look at that did you all have a vision
of a prophecy also in the asha that's
right and I'm here to fight for Sonic
Underground even if I have to put my
life on the line welcome to the fight
Inuyasha
okay now who is the bed I have to
destroy today to bring honor to su it's
those guys over there apparently they
are called the boys I don't see what's
the big deal they don't look so tough to
me
[Music]
that they show more
sesshomaru what the hell are you looking
at eyes down here we need to evaluate a
plan of attack
you're right let's get back to work no
more distractions
Inuyasha who is that guy over there with
the boys he is my brother my twin
brother if he's your brother and why is
he with them did he not grow up with
Sonic Underground like you of course he
did everybody did but when he is with
them that I do not know it is very
likely that they are offering to give
him a chicken jingle shard in exchange
for his help during this fight once the
fight starts leave him to me I won't let
you guys down I promise
look what all of these people showed up
the one purpose to protect Sonic
Underground you are not alone in this
war we will stand our ground and defeat
the boys together you are right as
always
my lover don't look now at you guys but
I think there's something flying right
over us do you think it's the boys no
it's it's moving way too fast
it's flying so it must be a bird no it's
a plane no it's a Superman
[Music]
oh [ __ ] it's the Dark Knight and the Boy
Wonder
yeah yeah are you sure you want the poor
Batman you seem kind of tired
oh I'm sorry everyone
Alabama via the reals browser we had
your run here what has a ma'am avail
yeah [ __ ] ha ha that's a real shame if
you could fly like me you wouldn't have
that trouble at all ha ha yeah Superman
if I could flatter you Terry pretty
useful
but you can't
haha I'm just messing with you Batman
where am I
obi-wan obi-wan we want to tell quitting
but now Sportacus can't you see that a
meditating and [ __ ]
II wanted to ask you [ __ ] Padawan I guess
clunky so fitting big went of Stassen
main distinction of earlier I wish I
knew myself but I don't perhaps he's
running late
perhaps he is getting some training and
before he shows up
one thing is for sure however I sense a
great disturbance in the force
what do you mean you're having second
thoughts now you you guys never told me
we would be fighting and were like this
and beside I have school tomorrow you'd
better start making sense right now boy
because if you do not take a wild guess
where this sword
the legendary Tensei gun is going that's
right up your butt this isn't what you
said would happen Mr. Johnson you said
only the Sonic Underground would be here
not [ __ ] Superman that got to hold an
army
I'm going home before they rape our ass
I told you already that it's too late
kid you chose your path the minute you
grouped up with me did you think this
was going to be simple like some kind of
vacation did you want me to suck your
smelly balls well it looks to me like
you were misinformed
there will be no sucking of balls today
and no backing out like a poopy baby put
that gun away Mr. Johnson it won't do us
any good to attack one another like this
us turning against each other like this
is exactly what sounding and his friends
would want we might look different but
we are very much alike we have a common
goal so there isn't any time or reason
for us to attack each other is there
the heroes what's that say that again
which interesting you want to try that
again [ __ ] be quiet you damn hillbilly
you don't know anything about me
[Music]
you don't know what I've been through ah
hell I experienced up until now
oh my am I interrupting something
so you're the boys the ones bold enough
to stand up to us you I have to admit I
am a little underwhelmed how about you
tell us who the hell you are remove that
robe [ __ ]
it's Anakin Skywalker that's right it's
me the chosen one
I never liked Sonic Underground in the
first place I merely played the role of
their ally so that I could get close to
them and destroy them even if I believed
ooh which I don't what makes you think
we would let you become one of the boys
because they have an army and it's only
growing larger hey Mr. Johnson thanks
for buying me and my brothers way out of
jail we're here too what the hell is
this why is that jet die here as the one
who killed our sister DeeDee doodle
relax you [ __ ] Doodlebops he is here
on his own accord he wants to fight with
us apologies but I had to kill at least
one of you otherwise the Sonic
Underground may have suspected that
something was wrong that's fine she just
got in the way anyways let's finally put
an end to the Sonic Underground once and
for all
yes today is finally the day the one
we've all been awaiting for
the Joker has arrived everyone the clown
is in town now let's take down the Sonic
on the ground what's it doing just
standing around for
go get my pimp cold [ __ ] Mr. J you want
to join the boys sorry but we don't need
help from freaks dressed like clowns are
you kidding me you guys a challenge of
the Sonic Underground that's crazy
you'll give me some crazed like me who
wants that chance why are you keep
laughing [ __ ] you think we are funny or
something sob out then this is Johnson I
got a condition here take my card
Harry Harry Potter what's happening
what's going on over there
the look in your eyes tell me that you
know something why did that scowl just
form in the clouds above the boys it's
no ordinary cloud it's a death mark the
symbol of he-who-must-not-be-named
Voldemort it's all my fault
he followed me here Lord Voldemort is
coming to kill us all
forgive me su hey what's there to
apologize for Harry this just makes it
all the more exciting
nobody said it's easy being sounded
Underground speech
[Music]
so you're the man who chose to be hated
by the entire world because you don't
like Sonic Underground you must have a
big pair of balls I like that I really
do I love men with big balls so I
brought forth my evil army of death
eaters to help you in combat [ __ ] yet we
have an even larger army than the sound
Underground now that isn't all this is
my body Grindelwald he's powerful as
[ __ ]
what is it render walled what do you see
oh it's Dumbledore
I forgot that UN Dumbledore used to be
gay lovers but render walled don't let
your emotions stop you from killing him
actually here's a better idea
turn that lust into her age destroy him
rape him with great force show that
Dumbledore who the real buses make him
call you dandy while you slap his butt
the games are over Mr. Johnson we will
give you one last chance to change your
ways release jeers papa and leave
forever if you do we can just forget all
of this ever happened no it's far too
late for that Hedgehog I never go back
on my promises and I'm not starting now
Jared we debut a job to do you were
supposed to kill Manik the Hedgehog but
you didn't now I will hold up my end of
the promise your bomb is finished he
will die right here no I can't I won't
do that passage I've seen so much death
and destruction today I can't bear to
see any more I hope you [ __ ] [ __ ] no
wait a male will chase you to the ends
of the earth the time for talking is
over old man it's time for you to make
peace Jared say goodbye to your pop the
man that you loved all so much put the
gun down we can't still talk this over
nobody has to die
you
[Music]
Goddamnit you [ __ ] green goblin [ __ ]
you
go away
[Applause]
they whip the rahmatan consumer go me
for spell D Kappa
- you [ __ ] I did it
hey are you watching [ __ ] away I beat up
the enemy
are you proud of me of course I am
consumer Yami boy Eva and we alo a
buffoon of you
good any caution I am freaking what are
their first irrelevant J so if you could
after consumer consumer you after FST
was the good a we hope you're [ __ ] us
help me
no dear Lord somebody please save my
life folder a hurry you have to cast a
spell or something do it quickly please
econ consumer and a looter Fiona she/he
contest a spell if you don't wanna
Sheila damn it God [ __ ] damn it holy
[ __ ] I don't want to die like this I
have it so much to live for
Oh No Kanchana is in trouble I won't let
you hurt any one of my friends
now have a taste of my most powerful
spell
hi I can't hold it much longer my power
isn't enough can't show me you have to
run if not the bullet is going to hit
right and your disgusting butt crack
stop it
has done nothing Junior crazy because we
live in a society Batman wait if you
don't like sock Underground everybody
hates you and you all just sort of sit
down and take it like good little boys
well I'm tired of it Batman I'm tired of
this and that's one cue you know he's
choking me I can't breathe you see Ben
and deep down we're all the same we all
hates all congrat you think deep down
telling yourself that Batman we both
know your lines Sonic come over here I
need to tell you something important
what's up Snape I talked with Sportacus
and he wanted me to pass on to you this
important message you and Bartleby need
to have butt sex in the middle of the
battlefield if you do this war will come
to an end I don't understand what do you
mean Sonic and Bartleby your love for
each other is so powerful that if you
two have sex for exactly 45 minutes you
have the power to turn back time and
change the course of the universe you
can make it as if this war never
happened
this is something only you can do as
Bartleby's personal [ __ ] it is however
dangerous so getting to the middle of
the battlefield where you can be [ __ ]
in the
will be hard however if you stay behind
me I can protect you do you think you
can do that Sonic you've got it
Professor snape let's do this it seems
as though they have a plan I must stop
them
for the boys so long fat [ __ ] psychic
look out
[Music]
I should go help Bart levy maybe he's in
trouble without me No what the hell am I
thinking
Bart levy can handle all this himself I
need to focus on my own mission I need
to get to the center of the battlefield
so Bart levy can [ __ ] my ass
no whoa
well well well if it isn't Sonic the
Hedgehog I wasn't expecting to see you
so soon I have to admit though I am
quite happy to have the honors of
killing you myself
damn you Grindelwald you'll pay for what
you just did you son of a [ __ ]
unfortunately for you fat boy I have no
intention of paying for my crimes
you
[Applause]
quick Sonic the Hedgehog come with me if
you want to live before I go with you
tell me who the hell you are
why are you saving me I am simply a man
who doesn't want you today just yet that
is all you need to know you are not even
going to tell me your name and yet you
expect me to come with you for all I
know you could be working with a boys
fine then I will tell you my name is the
demon of darkness and this guy over here
is one of my two demon [ __ ] just one
where's the other one the other one is
back at my castle of darkness
cleaning my royal throne you've asked it
do you really think I'm letting you
escape after almost running me over like
that
[Applause]
Avada Kedavra
demon of darkness are you okay
no no way it can't be dr. Robotnik all
this time you were the demon of darkness
why are you wearing this mask if anybody
is going to kill you Sonic my rival it's
going to be me not a couple of white
boys so I decided to fight alongside you
but I was too much of a coward to show
my face you shouldn't be embarrassed
Robotnik today we are all in this
together we're a team a team really how
silly that you think I would ever even
consider being on a team with you Sonic
but if it's only for today maybe I could
do it well what are you just standing
around here for Sonic don't you have to
get to the tent so your lover Bart levy
can bang you in your big plump of cheeks
what took you so long bitch I was
starting to get bored
bend over before rabbit but fools don't
you realize how defenseless you are
parking in a tent like that I've had a
cadaver whoa are you okay speak to me
you you little Jamaican [ __ ] why don't
you do us all a favor and go back to
your own country Knuckles the Echidna
I have been waiting for this day for so
long the day that I can finally kill you
the day that I can finally get my
revenge the day I can make you suffer I
don't even know who the [ __ ] you are
but I take it that you must be one of
the boys which means if you're really
willing to fight I won't hesitate to
stick my fist up your smelly butt
so you you don't even remember me after
making me suffer the way I did I think I
would remember a [ __ ] eight-year-old
in a green goblin costume that smells
like poop
[Applause]
I can only imagine how it is to be with
you from the first day I saw your face I
knew this love was true
you know Billy I get you always hated me
but I never would expect you to be one
of the boys I guess that makes two of us
never did I think I would get a chance
to destroy you like this but you know
what they say Manic everything happens
for a reason perhaps we were destined to
fight on this day perhaps you were
destined to die by my hands perhaps you
were destined to suck my big-ass balls
and call me daddy come here [ __ ] I
[Music]
didn't want to have to do that belief
but that doesn't mean I didn't like it
you and me don't have to fight we can't
talk it out no Manik I I have to do this
I I have to kill you
[Music]
I will give you one more chance if you
won't listen to me then maybe you will
listen to him
hello my son father why are what are you
doing here I heard that you got mixed up
with some bad people so I was worried
for you
you worried about me huh like I would
believe that now why is that so hard to
believe you're my son my precious boy I
love you very much why do you think
because you treat me like I'm garbage
every day you beat me and make my life
hell all for your own selfish gain
you tell me what to do and if I fail you
beat me up again or sometimes even pee
on me is that how you really feel son I
thought you liked it I didn't know you
felt this way
shut up you stupid father
[Music]
stop it Lee he's had enough leave him
alone no Manik leave it be this is my
punishment as a horrible father
[Music]
that is right [ __ ] now I'm your daddy
I'm going to make you feel the same pain
I did for so many years
[Music]
[Applause]
I'm sorry Billy but in the end you left
me with no other choice
dandy I feel cold am I going to die
no oh goodness no son daddy will save
you he was pierced through the heart
nothing can save his life now
not even your love dandy everything his
dark is at night yes the Sun is going
down and now it is time to Sleet my son
your long fight is over dad tomorrow can
we watch Sonic Underground DVDs like we
used to you can bet your huge [ __ ]
ass we can son
[Music]
thank you Manic the Hedgehog for showing
my son the light for saving him from the
path of darkness
a Veronica upon Issus if I catch him
this war is over come here Mr. Johnson
oh why would your top ruining unfilled
Mallika man give it up Mr. Han us where
we also London if you'll try anything
funny
we'll put you in tears no come with us
you are under arrest for taken in maceió
committed that is unless you're world
rather futile side that's hilarious
you [ __ ] actually thought you had me
on the run well I have news for you
truth is I lured you here so that I
could take you out all at once now which
one of you shall I play with first you
we you either you're one they find them
but just so you know I spent two weeks
trading at the YMCA also I could defeat
you Charles Hedgehog my rival he won't
abate any other way
let go of me so I can kill you it's your
fault Trevor is dead you better shut
your face or I will choke the life out
of you boy don't email money you owe me
pillows no I can't do this if we kill
him now this war is over we have to take
these chances no matter how small it may
be if you miss him then I'm [ __ ] dead
you [ __ ]
you better not shoot my smelly ass don't
delete it stolen heroes Norma [ __ ]
Sonic Manic and Sonia you three taught
me how to fight for what I believed in
that's why I wanted to repay you to help
you for all the times you helped me but
I wasn't much help in this fight was I
I'm sorry no it can't be but it is
Cyrus is dead why why did you do it
Cyrus why does this have to happen to us
a virgin a key Toto free it is lagarto
Minolta told Lincoln Domingo tees
[Music]
damnit
I can't still fight I'm not through just
yet look around you all of this chaos
and destruction you have caused you're
wrong this isn't what I wanted all I
wanted was revenge for my little brother
because you [ __ ] ran over him with
your car and now he can't walk anymore I
already told you [ __ ] that he drove up
into my driveway and rammed into my car
himself you don't understand what I had
to go through for my younger brother I
dedicated everything to becoming the
perfect brother I worked hard and
studied my ass off so that I could
provide for him
my brother he looked up to me I was his
hero I couldn't have been more happy
everything was going so well in my life
I followed in the footsteps of my father
I trained to become a doctor
eventually I graduated and earned enough
money to buy my brother something he
always wanted a bicycle from Wahlberg I
just couldn't wait to give it to him for
his birthday so I surprised him with it
early we took it out for a quick spin
little did we know it would be his first
and last ride
the bike was in pieces and my brother
was paralyzed for the rest of his life
I was scared to tell my father but I
knew I had to when I did I was spanked
by daddy's belt the pain was nothing
however to what I had done to my brother
what he did next was unforgivable
he turned the belt on my bro knowing
full well that that would hurt me more
than any belt to the butt cheeks
cool I don't give a [ __ ] Elena Elena me
Elena
this Beach Wat Arun yo Alberto Domingo
so Mateen so team Orson
hahaha now that I have the Royal scepter
in my possession
nobody can defeat me nice catch Charlie
this is why you've always been my
right-hand man now as the leader of a
boys I demand you hand me over that
Royal scepter nah I don't think I will
in fact I think I'll [ __ ] kill you
listen here bud
you were never my leader I was playing
you from the start I will give you one
thing though
you were a useful pun but unfortunately
pawns aren't useful this far into the
game goodbye Mr. Johnson or should I
call you [ __ ]
[Music]
I'm evil akiza's Mr. constant come on
Elena let's get the Manic Hedgehog that
is your name isn't it
Lord Voldemort what the hell do you want
I just wanted to know we all wanted to
apologize for everything we've done for
all the people that we've killed today
in cold blood
all of us bad guys came together because
we had one thing in common we all hated
you guys the sounding Underground but
fighting you made us realize something
the great thing about Sonic Underground
is that it's about love it was right in
front of our faces all along but we were
too scared to face it unlike you
you guys fought together as one while
Charlie turned down all of us the moment
he got power so please let us help you
defeat Charlie let us show you our
newfound love for Sonic Underground it
takes a big pair of balls to admit you
like Sonic Underground in a world where
Sonic Underground fans are looked down
upon by society
so because you admitted it we have no
choice but to accept you into our again
I just hope you are already Sonic
Underground fans face even more
discrimination than black people
[Music]
how sweet of you all to come together to
fight me I should be honored or rather
it's you [ __ ] who should be honored
to die by my hand if they buddy look
appears from sexy-looking no studying of
tanta
[Music]
[Applause]
it's him it's the real Tamers12345 one two
three four five he's here to save us
everyone can you believe it you bad guys
made the right choice joining the saw
kinda round one you did cuz I was gonna
kill all of you
but that's the good thing about Sonic on
ground it will comes everybody even if
you're black although if you're gonna be
fighting for South come around then
everybody needs medallions
[Music]
as long as the world's turning
sigh
the fire burning
[Music]
explain
and you'll say
take my
[Music]
Sonia Manny
how stupid can the two of you be leaving
home without your medallion so you
worked out of [ __ ] I see Sonic and
Bobby all having sex to turn back time
pretty cool and I got a front row seat
to the goods hey [ __ ] we are about to
hit the 45-minute mark when we do we
going back in time on [ __ ] so you better
prepare you're talking math all right
here we go Beach we only got one chance
for this so let's give it our best shot
Bart levy I think it's working
keep it up [ __ ] stop talking your only
job is to be quiet and get sucked in the
US
Bart Levy what's what's happening
we broke the time barrier Beach get
ready to cross over
[Music]
stop stop
hey I think it worked we seem to be in
the past yes back to where this all
started the day your family built a
haunted house better than Mr. Jones and
and destroyed his life we should get to
work if we destroy your family's haunted
house then Mr. Johnson will never be
defeated by you and go on a quest for
revenge against your family start
tearing it apart
I will keep watch to make sure nobody
sees your fat ass Bart levy look there's
my bro in his bacon costume from last
year I'm going to go say hi
ow what was that for Bartleby don't you
know the most basic rule of time travel
Beach whatever you do in the past change
is the future that is why we cannot be
seen now step aside so I can put an end
to this madness my feet hurt it's 7:00
p.m. and I should be home drinking
rosebud tea not saving the world again
let's get out of here Beach
[Music]
go away
at long last the Sonic Underground
finally will come to an end
what's happening to me it's almost like
like I'm fading away
look you guys something is wrong with
Charlie
hey Sonic ant bartelby are coming out of
the tent maybe they had something to do
with it hey bro glad to see you survived
getting [ __ ] in the ass for 45 minutes
ha ha 45 minutes is nothing bartelby can
[ __ ] me days on end it looks like what
me and Bart levy did in the past worked
the boys were never formed so they are
fading away and he is weak enough now
that we can defeat him in one fail swoop
just as the prophecy says defeat the
last of the boys and save our world you
ready to finish this my green bro I have
always been ready my blue bro
go on Sonic Underground show us what it
means to be heroes it is your duty to
finish this Sonic Underground chick has
[ __ ] us rape that's some of a [ __ ]
[Music]
what do you get when you cross Sonic on
the ground with a society that doesn't
give a [ __ ] about it you get what you
[ __ ] deserve [ __ ] after so long
the prophecy has finally been fulfilled
II will finally top-1 LFO hard work
finally pay off of course none of this
would have been possible if it wasn't
for Bart LD so what's going to happen
now that's right we changed the past and
that affected the boys what about Gus I
regret to inform you that we too will be
affected within just a few hours
everyone but Bart LD will lose their
memories of what happened here
eat that we owe you one he buffed lb
boozled onion and zucchini memo because
he was the one who did this changed the
past and saved us all Sonic and Bart
levy their love is so powerful as [ __ ]
that began to fight fate itself
everybody that died here today even
those who sided with evil will be
brought back to life and be given a
second chance and maybe just maybe this
time they will see the light that is
Sonic Underground if there is one thing
I know for sure is that Sonic
Underground is the [ __ ] [ __ ]
you
[Music]
drifting in the open side
whoa
[Music]
we could travel back
born from the same branch and leave
[Music]
thank you so much for inviting us all
over for dinner Elina don't mention it
hey kids have any of you seen Wes on the
can bar cubby went in ice almost ready I
have no idea I think they said something
about going stargazing together to
celebrate our victory against the boys
or some [ __ ] the boys who are you
talking about Manik who are the boys
hey Uncle Chuck who are the boys they
avoid what if Opie old donkey now with
Roy leaky leg and gosh I don't know for
some reason I just feel like I'm
forgetting something really important
Bart levy do you think what will be one
set is true will we all really lose our
memories well everybody but you I mean
well it does make sense after all I did
do all the work myself since I changed
the course of history by banging your
cute little ass
you
what's wrong bitch you seem a little bit
sad Oh Bart levy I was just thinking
it's pretty sad knowing that I'll soon
forget everyone I met today they were
all such good people and not just that
soon I will lose something even more
important something dear to my heart
since we changed the past and never met
the boys that means all the memories you
and I made all the adventures we shared
for the past few years I won't remember
any of that either will I
Bart Libby don't grab each you may
forget but that only gives us the excuse
to make more memories together and
besides even when you do forget
everything that happened don't forget
the time I'm the only one in the entire
world who will remember everything so
someday I will tell you all about this
great battle we fought in together
Oh Bart Levy thank you thank you so much
Bart levy what's going on why are we
sitting outside again
why does it feel like I've been crying
and my butt hurts it almost feels like
you banged me in the ass for 45 minutes
straight
uh-huh that's because I just did bitch
did you already forget I just got back
from a business trip and [ __ ] your
cute little ass till you passed out
hehehe is that so no wonder my butt
hurts so bad the stars are beautiful
tonight aren't they
yes they sure are but not as beautiful
as I am beneath the moon that's true
Bart levy there is nothing in this world
as beautiful as you I love you
on that night I told my Beach that I
would tell him all about the war and the
memories he lost but after some thought
I realized that I should never tell him
him or anyone else because it would only
bring nothing but pain all those
memories the memories of the world
before it was changed
they will stay forever locked in my
heart because I am special I am the only
man strong enough to carry the weight of
the world's memories on my shoulders and
one of a kind some would even call me a
king or a God because I'm so great and
kind I didn't choose to be this great
but it is a burden I will have to bear
for my entire life
my name is Bobby Montclair of Dresden
and it is my story
[Music]